amhfcu.org 2006-09-23

# Privacy Policy

|   

|  | 

| 

American Heritage Federal Credit Union  
On-Line Privacy Statement  
  
---  
Because the privacy of our Members and other visitors to this website is of utmost importance, American Heritage Federal Credit Union has adopted the following privacy policy:  
  
_**A Private Note to our Members:**_  
| American Heritage Federal Credit Union is committed to making available financial products and services that will enable you to meet your financial needs and reach your financial goals. Protecting personal information and using it in a manner consistent with your expectations is a high priority for everyone associated with your Credit Union.

As a Member of American Heritage FCU, you also have a responsibility to safeguard your financial information. To ensure that you can rely upon the quality of products and services we make available, American Heritage FCU stands behind the following privacy policy:

 ****

****
  * **American Heritage FCU will collect only the personal information that is necessary to conduct our business.** That means just what is necessary to provide competitive financial products and services - no more.

****

****
  * **American Heritage FCU will protect your personal information.** We will maintain strong security controls to ensure that Member information in our files and computers is protected. Where appropriate, we will use security coding techniques to protect against unauthorized access to personal records, ensure accuracy and integrity of communications and transactions and protect member confidentiality.

****
  * **You will always have access to your information.** As a Member of American Heritage FCU, you will always have the opportunity to review your information and make necessary changes to ensure that our records are complete and accurate.

****
  * **American Heritage FCU will only share information when it is absolutely necessary.** We will only share information to administer the products and services we provide, when required to do so by the government, or when we partner with other businesses to offer a broader array of products and services.

****
  * **American Heritage FCU will partner only with businesses that follow strict confidentiality requirements.** The businesses we select will offer products designed to enhance our Members' economic well-being. Under no circumstances will we authorize these firms to charge your account without your consent, and we will not sell member information to telemarketing firms.

****
  * **American Heritage FCU will offer you a choice in how your information is used.** Any Member of American Heritage FCU may elect to keep information from being shared with business partners. We will inform you on how to exercise your choice, and we will take reasonable steps to make sure your requests are followed. At least once a year, we will remind all Members of your right to choose.
